<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Star Wars - Fully Functional Lightsabers</name>
  <author>Jecrell and Xen</author>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <packageId>projectjedi.lightsabers</packageId>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>jecrell.jecstools</packageId>
      <displayName>JecsTools</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/932008009</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://patreon.com/jecrell</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>1.21.0.0 (02-29-2020)

	Adds constructable full-SFX lightsabers that can activate, load crystals, and deflect bullets.

	Thanks to Jedi Master Ailan for his direction and inspiration in the creation of this mod. Without his help and support this would have never happened.

	C# Programming by Jecrell.
	C# Fixes, Assets, and XML by Xen.
    Logo/Art designed by Harrison Gaushell (harrisongaushell.com)

	Patreon Patrons:
	Jedi Master Ailan, Shane Malley, Michin, TheDayDude, Dakota Pohlman, Falloutmonk, Legless, Slick Liquid,  Don Butterblume, Karol Rybak, Mathias Broxvall, Nemuri Hime, Hannah Forster, Christian Hermansen, NiNe Bottles of Rum, Populous25, Steven James, Marcus Sireanu, Michael Lauder, Thom Black

Thank you to my Patrons for supporting me in my efforts. Without you, none of this would be possible.

These are the most excellent rim dwellers who support me: 
Marcus Bell, RainerWingel, Dalton Johnson, Chris Seieroe, Robin Gleeson, Robert Alessi, Lea Stannard, Teres, David Silberstein, Sam, Kiya Nicoll, Matt Harris, Paul Fenwick, Grendalloffen, Don Homer, Josh McCabe, Elodie, Gothi, J, Michael Paugh, Audrin Navarro, Михаил Юрченко, Calum, Tim Stillson, Adam Bliss, Populous25, Marcus Sireanu, Maaxar, John Kanady, Midgeman, Dick Jones, Patrick, TinyFloatingTurtle, Nathan Getman, LionsFate, Sharp Spook, Cristina Shaver, Mark, George Chong Chuang Ming, Oliver White, roxxploxx, Emily Shaw, Karol Rybak, Justin Andres, Marcus Regan, Robin Hager, Allic, Austin Harbert, E_T, Alex Mederer, Alexander, Toss Antilles

========================
Changelog
========================
1.21.0.0 (02-29-2020)
========================
Updates Star Wars Lightsabers to work with the newest version of RimWorld. RimWorld v1.1.

1.20.0.0 (10-19-2018)
========================
Initial release for RimWorld 1.0.

</description>
</ModMetaData>